A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.31 (A2005) FA491
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2005.072: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1996-2005; AC.2005.072; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3741, R3751-R3755.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RESIDENT (Metcalf, Thomas R.), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Molotch, Harvey), 1998-2003 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Nandy, Ashis), 1998-2000 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Nochlin, Linda), 1996-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Nvan, Thanh), 1998-2005 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Obermeyer, Carla Makhlouf), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Oguibe, Oluchukwu Olu), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Ostriker, Alicia Suskin), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Panikkar, Kandivur Narayana), 1998-2000 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Pantin, Yolanda) (CO-RESIDENT: Torres, Ana Teresa), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Perry, Ruth), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Premdas, Ralph R.), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Raphael, Judith), 1998-2000 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Ren, Donglai), 1998-2000 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Riche, Martha Farnsworth), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Roberts, Robert Edmund), 1998-2000 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Rohl, John C. G.), 1998-2000 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Rosen, Lawrence), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Ross, Dorothy), 1998-2000 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Salovey, Peter), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Sanchez-Gutierrez, Carlos), 1998-2001 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Sant'Anna, Affonso Romano), 1998-2000 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Scheffler, Richard M.), 1998-1999 (Box R3754)
    - RESIDENT (Segal, Sheldon J.), 1998-1999 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Sherwin, Susan), 1998-1999 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Shiloah, Amnon), 1998-2004 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Shohat, Ella Habiba) (CO-RESIDENT: Stam, Robert), 1998-1999 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Smaling, Eric Marc Alexander), 1998-2002 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Smith, Dave Jeddie), 1998-1999 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Solomon, Zahava), 1998-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Spiridon, Monica), 1998-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Stein, Judith E.), 1998-1999 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Steiner, Henry J.), 1998-2001 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Sternhell, Zeev), 1997-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Stetsenko, Ekaterina A.), 1998-1999 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Stone, Carl), 1998-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Sullivan, Chip), 1998-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Sussman, Elizabeth), 1999-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Teitelbaum, Richard Lowe), 1999-2004 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Throsby, Charles David), 1999-2001 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Tiruchelvam, Neelan), 1998-1999 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Tishkov, Valery A.) (CO-RESIDENT: Olcott, Martha Brill), 1997-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Toolan, David S.), 1998-2001 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Vitug, Marites D.), 1998-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Wellman, Barry), 1999-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Yzaguirre, Raul H.), 1998-2000 (Box R3755)
    - RESIDENT (Zhanq, Yonghua), 1998-1999 (Box R3755)
- AC.2005.073: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1996-2003; AC.2005.073; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3743.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.073.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 98039 #15 - WORLD CONFERENCE ON RELIGION AND PEACE - KOSOVO PROJECT, 1996-2001 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98038 #64 - HORIZON CENTER FOR STUDIES AND RESEARCH (JORDAN) - t{SEARCH PROJECT ON "IMAGE OF THE OTHER", 1999-2001 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98036 #870 - KYOMUHENDO, GRACE BANTEBYA - ACA: CAUSES OF MATERNAL MORTALITY IN UGANDA, 1999-2003 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98037 #51 - CASA ATABEX ACHE - NETWORK OF GIRLS AND WOMEN IN MOTT HAVEN, BRONX, 1998-2000 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98038 #66 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP ON IRAN AND MIDDLE EAST, 1999-2001 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98038 #72 - WOMEN LIVING UNDER MUSLIM LAWS (FRANCE) - INTERNATIONAL DOCUMENTATION AND PUBLICATIONS PROGRAM, 1997-2002 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98038 #73 - VAN LEER JERUSALEM INSTITUTE (ISRAEL) - MEETINGS TO DEVELOP ARAB-ISRAELI CULTURAL DIALOGUE, 1999-2002 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98041 #74 - MARKET THEATRE LABORATORY (SOUTH AFRICA) - FIELDWORK PROGRAM IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1996-2001 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98041 #86 - CARIBBEAN PUBLISHERS NETWORK (TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO) - BC CONFERENCE: STRATEGIC PLANNING MEETING OF THE NETWORK, 2000-2002 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98041 #87 - TRANSAFRICA FORUM - CULTURAL EXCHANGES BETWEEN CUBA AND U.S., 1999-2001 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98041 #88 - INTERNATIONAL AFRICAN INSTITUTE (ENGLAND) - SEMINAR ON AFRICAN CULTURAL PUBLISHING, 2000-2001 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98048 #11 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - BC CONFERENCE: INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY AND GLOBAL BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1998-2001 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98048 #14 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR ACQUISITION OF AGRI-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - GENETICALLY MODIFIED RICE AND PRO-VITAMIN A IN ENDOSPERM, 2000-2002 (Box R3743)
    - RF 98048 #5 - CENTER FOR THE APPLICATION OF MOLECULAR BIOLOGY TO INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURE (AUSTRALIA) - ESTABLISH INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY STRATEGIC OFFICE, 1998-2002 (Box R3743)
- AC.2005.074: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2004; AC.2005.074; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3742, R3744, R3745.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.074.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 98028 #310 - AMERICAN MUSEUM OF THE MOVING IMAGE - DIGITAL MEDIA CONFERENCE AND EXHIBITION PLANNING, 1998-2001 (Box R3742)
    - RF 98030 #8 - ENTERPRISE FOUNDATION - ABILITY OF NON-PROFITS TO PROVIDE JOBS THROUGH REVENUE-GENERATING ENTERPRISES, 1997-2005 (Box R3742)
    - RF 98027 #350 - DANCING IN THE STREETS - "PICTURE RED HOOK", 1998-2002 (Box R3742)
    - RF 98028 #311 - JACOBS, KEN - ARCHIVAL AND EXPERIMENTAL WORK IN FILM AND DIGITAL MEDIA, 1998-2001 (Box R3742)
    - RF 98029 #38 - SAN FRANCISCO STATE UNIVERSITY - URBAN CURRICULUM COMMUNITY BUILDING ORGANIZATION CAPACITY BUILDING PROJECT, 1999-2004 (Box R3742)
    - RF 98031 #51 - COUNCIL FOR BASIC EDUCATION - STANDARDS-BASED TEACHER EDUCATION PROJECT, 1997-2002 (Box R3742)
    - RF 98031 #51 - COUNCIL FOR BASIC EDUCATION - STANDARDS-BASED TEACHER EDUCATION PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1997-2002 (Box R3742)
    - RF 98031 #52 - IMPACT II - THE TEACHERS NETWORK - TEACHERS AND IMPROVEMENT OF STUDENT ACHIEVEMENT; CONNECT EDUCATIONAL POLICY TO CLASSROOM POLICY, 1999-2001 (Box R3742)
    - RF 98032 #30 - CHATHAM-SAVANNAH YOUTH FUTURES AUTHORITY - NEIGHBORHOOD IMPROVEMENT ASSOCIATION, 1998-2004 (Box R3742)
    - RF 98049 #33 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - PROGRAM ON VACCINES AND OTHER BIOLOGICALS, 1998-2003 (Box R3744)
    - RF 98049 #33 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - PROGRAM ON VACCINES AND OTHER BIOLOGICALS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2003 (Box R3744)
    - RF 98050 - AIDS AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH RESEARCH BY DEVELOPING-COUNTRY SCIENTISTS, 1989-2002 (Box R3744)
    - RF 98050 - AIDS AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH RESEARCH BY DEVELOPING-COUNTRY SCIENTISTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1989-2002 (Box R3745)
- AC.2005.076: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2004; AC.2005.076; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, R3756-R3760.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - BC TEAM: Aborigines of Arnhem Land, Northern Australia: Ecological Studies of Hunter-Gatherers in Transition, 1997-1998 (Box R3756)
      Scope and Contents
      The formal title of this report includes a term considered offensive towards Aboriginal Australian people. The Aboriginal Australian peoples specifically referenced by the report may be the Yolnu, Bininj, and Maung peoples. The language is retained because it is the official name of the work.
    - BC TEAM: Advancing Graduate Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing Education Internationally, 1996-1997 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: African Census Analysis Project, 1998-1999 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Belen Project, 1997-2000 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Beyond the Unitary State: New Patterns of Autonomy and Cooperation in Diverse European Regions, 1996-1998 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Book to Enable Future Leaders to Understand New and Emerging Viral Diseases, 1996-1999 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Building Sustainable Community through Communication Arts, 1995-1998 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Care of the Terminally Ill, 1994-1996 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Changing World of Work, 1998-2000 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Community-based Health Delivery in Rural Africa: Challenges and Prospects, 1998-1999 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Comparative Policy Framework for Managing Expansion of Metropolitan Regions in Pacific Asia, 1997-1998 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Comparative Study of Cooperative Approaches to Hazards and Environmental Management, 1994-1996 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Construction and Maintenance of Social Trust, 1995-1996 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Correlation of Karyotypic, Morphologic, and Clinical Features in Soft Tissue Sarcomas, 1996-1997 (Box R3756)
    - BC TEAM: Creating, Spreading, and Using Agricultural Technology in China, 1998-2000 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Death of the Father: An Anthropology of Changes in Political Authority (Second Meeting), 1995-2001 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Desert Songs, 1997-2000 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Developing a Strategy for Preserving Animal Insulin, 1995-1998 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Distrust, 1996-1997 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Dragon Bond Rite, 1996-2000 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Effect of Dioxin on the Human Immune System, 1995-1996 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Exploring the Potential of Integrated Crop Management, 1998-1999 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Future Directions Committee of the International Plant Protection Congresses, 1996-1998 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Global Network on Health Equity, 1995-1996 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Graduate Education in Oceanography in Developing Countries as a Means to Understand Global Environmental Problems, 1998-2002 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Health Sector Interventions for Adolescent Health and Preparation for the WHO Study Group on Programming for Adolescent Health, 1995 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Historic Site Museums of Conscience, 1998-2001 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Improving Women's Health in the Post-Cairo Era, 1998 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: India and Pakistan: Oppottunities in Economic Growth, Technoloav and Securitv (First Meeting), 1996-1997 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: India and Pakistan: Opportunities in Economic Growth, Technoloav and Security (Second Meeting), 1997-1999 (Box R3757)
    - BC TEAM: Informed Choice in Family Planning Service Delivery, 1998-1999 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Intercultural Music, 1992-1995 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Interpenetration of Science and Philosophy of Science, 1997-1998 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Islam and the Modern World, 1996 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Latino Academic Advancement in the 1990s, 1993-1994 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: LEAD Task Force, 1996-1997 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Mapping China's Past: A Cartographic Reconstruction of Chinese History, 1998-2002 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Model of the Best Apprenticeship Practices for Training Youth in Skilled Occupations, 1996-1997 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Molecular Epidemiological Surveillance Network for Birth Defects in Latin America, 1998-2000 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: New History of Latin American Art: Issues and Problems, 1996-1998 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Operationalizing Cairo and Beijing - A Training Initiative in Gender and Reproductive Health, 1998-1999 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Organization and Implementation of an International Human Organ Donor Surveillance Committee, 1996-1997 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Oxygen Transport Across the Pulmonary Epithelium, 1994-1999 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Political and Cultural Dimensions oflnternational Health Policy, 1998-2000 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Political and Cultural Dimensions of International Health Policy: Lessons from the Child Immunization Initiative, 1996-1998 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Political Learning and Redemocratization in Contemporary Latin America, 1995-1996 (Box R3758)
    - BC TEAM: Prospective, Stock-Taking Review of Education in Africa, 1999-2000 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Raising the Moral and Political Stature of Economic Analysis in Allocating Health Services, 1996-2000 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Reconciling Freedom of Speech and Equality, 1995-2000 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Reproductive Rights as Human Rights: Implementing a Cross-cultural, Multi-country Research and Action Proiect, 1993-1996 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Role of Customary Law in the Local Self-Governing Sustainable Development Model, 1997-1999 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Socio-Economic and Security Developments in Russian Atomic Cities, 1998-2004 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Strategic Planning for the Medical Women's International Association, 1995-1998 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Swedish Philanthropy, 1997-1998 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Troja Island, Prague: Community Revitalization Project, 1996-1998 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Use of Short Chain Fatty Acids in Oral Rehydration, 1995-1996 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Why Organizations Have Varied in Their Capacity to Make Major Discoveries in Biomedical Science, 1995-1997 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Wind Energy and the Landscape: Reconciling Nature and Technology, 1996-2001 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Women Living Under Muslim Laws, 1993-1994 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Women Workers in the Informal Sector, 1996-1997 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Women's World European Team Meeting, 1998-2001 (Box R3759)
    - BC TEAM: Youth and Sexuality in the Developing World: Case Study in Sri Lanka, 1995-1997 (Box R3759)
    - CONFERENCE: Arab Intellectuals on Liberal Alternatives and the Role of the Individual, 1998-2000 (Box R3759)
    - CONFERENCE: Causes and Consequences of Early Retirement: What Policymakers Know and What They Need to Know, 1998-2000 (Box R3759)
    - CONFERENCE: Cause Lawyering and the State in Global Perspective, 1998-1999 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Civic Participation and Civil Society: A Comparative Perspective on the Independent Sector and the Political Incorporation of Marginalized Populations, 1997-2003 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Constitution-making, Conflict, and Transition in Divided Societies, 1997-2001 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Exercise of Universal Jurisdiction in Respect of Gross Human Rights Offences, 1998-2001 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: From Extreme Povetty to Sustainable Livelihoods, 1999-2000 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Global Investing: A New Reality Post-Y2K, 1998-2000 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Globalization and Culture, 1998-1999 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Global Staff Retreat, 1999 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Identifying Objectives to 2010 for the Human Rights Movement in the OSCE Area, 1997-2000 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Public/Private Sector Collaboration in Contraceptive Research and Development: A New Partnership (Bellagio III), 1998-2003 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Regional Peacekeeping, National Demilitarization, and Development in Africa, 1998-2002 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Religion and Modernity: Rethinking Secularization, 1998-2002 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Sustainable Agriculture: New Paradigms and Old Practices, 1998-1999 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Turkey Today: Challenges and Opportunities, 1997-1999 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Understanding Unemployment and Working Time: A Cross-Country Comparative Study, 1999-2000 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Underwriting and Coordination Post-Conflict Recovery, 1997-1999 (Box R3760)
    - CONFERENCE: Visions of Jerusalem, 1998-2003 (Box R3760)
- AC.2005.078: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2004; AC.2005.078; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3746
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.078.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 98052 #159 - ETTA-AKINAINA, FLORENCE EBAM - NEW DIRECTIONS IN GENDER RESEARCH IN AFRICA, 1999-2002 (Box R3746)
    - RF 98052 #165 - (FEMALE PARTICIPATION IN AFRICAN EDUCATION) - NEWSLETTER OF MINDS ACROSS AFRICA SCHOOL CLUBS PROJECT, 1999-2002 (Box R3746)
    - RF 98052 #169 - HANOI SCHOOL OF PUBLIC HEALTH (VIETNAM) - GIRLS' SEXUAL MATURATION AND MENSTRUAL PRACTICES, 2000 (Box R3746)
    - RF 98052 #192 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - BOOKLET ON HIV/AIDS EDUCATION FOR SCHOOLS, 2000-2001 (Box R3746)
    - RF 98055 #610 - CURARE: ESPACIO CRITICO PARA LAS ARTES - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1993-2001 (Box R3746)
    - RF 98055 #630 - UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON - MEETING, "THINKING RIGHTS, ENGAGING COMMUNITIES", 1999-2001 (Box R3746)
    - RF 99001 #712 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - BLAST RESISTANT RICE CULTIVARS IN VIETNAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3746)
    - RF 99001 #714 - RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (THAILAND) - MOLECULAR MARKER ASSISTED SELECTION AND FLOOD TOLERANCE IN RICE, 1998-2002 (Box R3746)
    - RF 99001 #715 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - AFRICAN RICE GALL MIDGE RESISTANCE GENES, 1995-2001 (Box R3746)
    - RF 99001 #726 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - MICROSATELLITE MARKERS FOR RICE, 1994-2003 (Box R3746)
    - RF 99001 #728 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - TRANSGENIC RICE WITH IMPROVED STEM BORER RESISTANCE, 1998-2001 (Box R3746)
- AC.2005.079: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2004; AC.2005.079; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3747, R3748, R3750.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.079.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 99001 #732 - INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL BIOLOGY (VIETNAM) - RICE GENE TECHNOLOGY, 1999-2002 (Box R3747)
    - RF 99001 #733 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - TRANSGENIC INDICA RICE PLANTS, 1996-2001 (Box R3747)
    - RF 99001 #748 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - MOLECULAR ANALYSIS OF "NEW PLANT TYPE" RICE, 1998-1999 (Box R3747)
    - RF 99001 #751 - NATIONAL CHEMICAL LABORATORY (PUNE) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1990-2000 (Box R3747)
    - RF 99001 #778 - SWISS FEDERAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (SWITZERLAND) - ENGINEERING VITAMIN AND MICRONUTRIENT-ENHANCED RICE, 1999-2001 (Box R3747)
    - RF 99001 #780 - DILLE, JOHN E., 1991-2000 (Box R3747)
    - RF 99003 #196 - WAGENINGEN AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (NETHERLANDS) - INTEGRATED NUTRIENT MANAGEMENT IN SEMI-ARID KENYA, 1999-2002 (Box R3747)
    - RF 99003 #200 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (DEPT. OF) - MALAWI MAIZE AGRONOMY TEAM, 1994-2000 (Box R3747)
    - RF 99005 - (INTEGRATED BANANA RESEARCH IN UGANDA) - ROLE OF PESTS AND PATHOGENS IN BANANA PRODUCTION, 1992-2001 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99005 #51 - INTERNATIONAL PLANT GENETIC RESOURCES INSTITUTE (ITALY) - GERMPLASM COLLECTION OF EAST AFRICAN HIGHLAND BANANAS, 2000-2002 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #152 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - F. ALBIDA AND TISSUE CULTURE, 1994-2003 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #168 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - OPPORTUNITIES FOR VERMICOMPOSTING IN MAIZE-BASED SYSTEMS, 1999-2002 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #169 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - PREDICTING LONG-TERM SOIL ORGANIC MATTER DYNAMICS, 1999-2002 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #173 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - NEMATODES AND COMMON BEANS IN SMALL SCALE FARMS, 1997-2002 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #179 - EDUARDO MONDLANE UNIVERSITY (MOZAMBIQUE) - ECOLOGY OF THE RED LOCUST IN THE OUTBREAK AREA OF THE BUZI-GORONGOZA, 1998-2003 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #184 - MOI UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - FOREST REGENERATION IN SHAMBA SYSTEM OF CROP PRODUCTION, 1999-2002 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #186 - EGERTON UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - CONSTRAINTS TO GROUNDNUT PRODUCTION, 1995-2002 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #189 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - STIPEND SUPPLEMENT FOR STUDENTS OF FORUM FOR AGRICULTURAL RESOURCE HUSBANDRY, 1995-2002 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #194 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - AGRICULTURAL RESOURCE MANAGEMENT IN SMALLHOLDER HIGHLAND SYSTEMS, 1994-2002 (Box R3748)
    - RF 99006 #198 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - RANGELAND REHABILITATION USING FORAGE/FODDER LEGUMES, 2000-2003 (Box R3748)
    - RF 96065 - COMMON ENTERPRISE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2000 (Box R3750)
- AC.2005.084: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2002; AC.2005.084; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3749, R3749A.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.084.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 99007 #45 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR INFORMATION ON COVER CROPS (HONDURAS) - WORKSHOP ON MUCUNA AND ANTINUTRITIONAL FACTORS, 2000-2002 (Box R3749)
    - RF 99007 #48 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - PUBLICATION, CASSAVA: AFRICA'S BEST KEPT SECRET, 2000-2002 (Box R3749)
    - RF 99008 - POLICY RESEARCH IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1993-1996 (Box R3749)
    - RF 99009 - POLICY RESEARCH AND DIALOGUE, 1993-2002 (Box R3749, Box R3749A)
    - RF 99009 - POLICY RESEARCH AND DIALOGUE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2002 (Box R3749A)
    - RF 99009 #196 - FAMILY CARE INTERNATIONAL - CAIRO PLUS 5 REPORT, 1998-2002 (Box R3749A)
    - RF 99009 #196 - FAMILY CARE INTERNATIONAL - CAIRO PLUS 5 REPORT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2002 (Box R3749A)
    - RF 99009 #202 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - FERTILITY DECLINE IN BANGLADESH AND WEST BENGAL, INDIA, 1996-2003 (Box R3749A)
    - RF 99009 #205 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - DIFFUSION AND IDEATIONAL CHANGE IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1995-2002 (Box R3749A)
    - RF 99009 #212 - HIVE COLLABORATIVE - WEB SITE PROMOTING SOUTH-SOUTH DEVELOPMENT, 1999-2002 (Box R3749A)
- AC.2005.089: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2004; AC.2005.089; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3761, R3762.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.089.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 99009 #213 - POPULATION CONCERN (ENGLAND) - NGO COLLABORATION WITH GOVERNMENTS, 1996-2002 (Box R3761)
    - RF 99009 #218 - UNITED NATIONS POPULATION FUND - CONSOLIDATION OF SOUTH-TO-SOUTH INITIATIVES, 1995-2001 (Box R3761, Box R3762)
    - RF 99009 #218 - UNITED NATIONS POPULATION FUND - CONSOLIDATION OF SOUTH-TO-SOUTH INITIATIVES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1995-2001 (Box R3761, Box R3762)
    - RF 99009 #225 - PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION OF CANADA - CREATE NGO TO PROMOTE CAIRO PROGRAMME OF ACTION, 1997-2001 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99012 - UNDERSTANDING CULTURES THROUGH MUSEUMS, 1987-1997 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99012 #215 - INTERNATIONAL FOLK ART FOUNDATION - EXHIBITION, "SIN NOMBRE: HISPANA AND HISPANO ARTISTS OF THE NEW DEAL ERA", 1998-2004 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99012 #238 - EN FOCO, INC. - COMMEMORATIVE PUBLICATION ON PHOTOGRAPHERS, 1999-2004 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99012 #242 - MUSEUM OF AMERICAN FOLK ART - "THE QUIET IN THE LAND: EVERYDAY LIFE, CONTEMPORARY ART AND PROJECTO AXE" IN BRAZIL, 1999-2003 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99014 #23 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - DATABASE OF ELECTION RETURNS FROM KEY STATES, 1999-2004 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99014 #27 - FOUNDATION FOR CONTEMPORARY RESEARCH (SOUTH AFRICA) - DEMOCRATIZING CIVIL SOCIETY, STIMULATING LOCAL ECONOMIES, 1999-2001 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99015 #42 - HAMILTON COLLEGE - CHANGING EMPLOYMENT PRACTICES AND QUALITY OF JOBS IN METROPOLITAN AND NON-METROPOLITAN COMMUNITIES IN CENTRAL NEW YORK, 1999-2000 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99015 #43 - WAYNE STATE UNIVERSITY - MAJOR AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER'S WORKPLACE STRATEGIES ON LOWER-SKILLED PRODUCTION WORKERS, 1999-2000 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99015 #44 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - "NEW MEDIA" WORKFORCE STUDY, 2000-2001 (Box R3762)
    - RF 99015 #51 - INSTITUTE OF DEVELOPMENT STUDIES (ENGLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: VALUE CHAIN RESEARCH, 2000-2002 (Box R3762)
- AC.2005.091: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2003; AC.2005.091; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3763.